Blessed by heaven and earth,
the Chaos Pearl was born.
The Supreme Lord split it into two.
The celestial energy
within became the Spirit Pearl,
while the demonic energy
formed the Demon Orb.
A Wrath of Heaven curse
was cast on the Demon Orb,
set to destroy it with
lightning in three years.
Later, due to Shen Gongbao's intervening,
the Demon Orb reincarnated as Nezha,
third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass.
The Spirit Pearl became Ao Bing,
also the third son of the Loong King.
By fate,
the two became best friends.
Nezha, influenced by his parents,
shed his demonic nature,
and saved Chentang Pass.
Together with Ao Bing,
they faced the Wrath of Heaven,
and at last
changed their destinies.
Though survived the wrath,
your bodies were destroyed...
without which
the soul will soon fade into oblivion.
The Sacred Lotus
protects and nurtures spirit.
I will now use it to recreate
your physical forms.
Wow.
Stunning.
Start up!
Something's off...
The lotus root must be powdered
to make your bodies.
with that hand?
Oh, don't worry.
I don't mind sticky foot,
a quick wash will fix it.
It's not your foot I care.
Did you just blow your nose with that hand?
No, nothing.
It's just lotus powder.
See?
Lotus powder.
It's ready to go.
Here, come on.
One booger for each of you.
I mean one serving.
Chop-chop! To save your souls.
I'd rather...
Pain in the ass, little bastard!
It works!
Hang on.
What is this?
Thanks to you.
I've been looking all over.
Time for shaping.
Flying Pig's memory is unmatched,
so is his carving skills.
Perfect renovation, right?
Thanks, Piggy.
Don't move, not fixed yet.
Master Immortal,
I've mobilized all of Chentang's forces
on guarding of Shen Gongbao
and the Eastern Sea Loongs.
Take it easy.
The Loongs are watching the Abyss monsters,
none of which would escape.
Shen Gongbao alone is no threat.
You should check this out.
Isn't this impeccable?
Woah!
He learned from the best.
But,
does it have to be exactly the same?
Can't you make me look better?
Huh?
Parents always pray good for kids, huh?
Right.
Make me tall and hunky.
Also hauntingly handsome.
A man must be strong and lofty.
As well as demure and mindful.
But also cute and lovable.
Can you all make up your mind?
Tall and hunky.
With a touch of handsomeness.
Strong and lofty.
Yet super adorable.
What's this?
Start your performance then.
Come on!
I should've taken over earlier.
DIY is always the best.
This could take a while.
Let's do you first.
You were born of the water element,
so you must be tempered by pure water.
Open Lotus!
Here we go.
Are you done?
Almost.
This version is surely the most dazzling,
but fine-tuning will take a long time.
How about we just use
the first one for now?
Yeah, the first version will do.
I agree.
Right.
You were born of the fire element,
so you must be refined in pure flames.
Sir!
Enemy has been spotted at sea.
It seems to be Shen Gongbao.
How many?
Just him.
How come?
Carry on with your spell.
We'll handle the intruder.
Master Immortal,
let me go plead with my master.
Don't move!
Before another incense
stick is fully burnt,
your body won't be fixed.
Shen Gongbao,
to what do we owe this honor?
Now that you know of
my plan with the Loongs,
I can't help but feel un... uneasy.
Chentang Pass is heavily guarded,
and Master Taiyi is within the city.
You, alone, won't accomplish much.
Who... who said I'm alone?
If they find out about the Spirit Pearl,
not only will you fail to avenge your son,
but the entire Eastern Loong Clan
will bear the blame.
When the truth comes out,
you'll be cast into the abyss purgatory,
surrounded by all your old "fellows".
Let's see how we welcome you.
Being stuck in Loong Palace...
How could you avenge your son?
Even I feel nervous for you.
You fools are in no place to gloat.
I was simply trying to help.
But it seems that you
don't appreciate it.
Hmm?
You must've forgotten what I'm capable of.
Ah!
I know this one.
The Sky... Sky... Sky...
Sky Splitting Claw.
Thank you.
Master Shen can take
this claw to Chentang Pass,
and use it to tear open
a rift leading back to me.
The Abyss Monsters can
then help you destroy your enemy.
The Abyss Monsters?
How... is that possible?
They were trapped by the Suppression Seal
for thousand years.
How could they possibly escape?
The Loongs... have they
already released them?
With the Sea-Stabilizing Chains binding us,
there's no chance for escape.
This is a win-win tactic.
What do you say, my brother?
You wouldn't be so generous.
Get to the point.
What's your price?
In this purgatory,
where flames burn our bodies,
every day feels like a year.
If you could slightly
lower the lava's heat,
easing our suffering,
we'd be willing to serve
you with all our might.
What's going on?
What is Shen Gongbao up to now?
Finally, we're out! Yay!
Bye-bye!
Vile.
We're doomed.
How will we explain this to General Li now?
Luckily no one saw us.
Here.
I'll break you arms
and then you break my legs.
We'll say the Yaksha did it.
Oh.
When the general sees how badly we're hurt,
he won't blame us anymore.
Try your best.
Hit harder!
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Master Immortal,
you're here!
Hee hee hee!
Ha ha ha!
He let the Yaksha get away!
Huh?
It was all your fault.
Who are you to play innocent?
Oh my,
Dumb and Dumber!
Hey!
You two boneheads!
Get over here and guard me!
Yes, Sir! Right away!
Show no mercy.
Shen Gongbao!
Ao Bing is not dead.
Chentang Pass and the Loongs
have no reason to fight.
Taiyi is rebuilding Ao
Bing's body right now.
Liar!
Hmm?
The shield...
No!
Master!
Ao Bing!
Master Taiyi has built me a new body.
Please, ceasefire.
I saved your disciple.
How will you thank me?
So,
that's Nezha in there?
Why, you ungrateful bastard!
Master!
They must die!
Ha ha ha!
You think you can break this shield?
Hit me! Come on!
No!
The aura...
Ao Bing!
Father!
I failed the mission to save our kind.
No.
None of that matters.
I just want you to be safe.
As long as you're here,
it's enough for me.
Open Lotus!
Your body, what is...
Please, he's literally a newborn.
How could he take a hit like that?
Ao Bing!
Hey! It's not ready yet!
Don't move! Don't move!
Ao Bing, what's going on?
Never move before fixed.
If your body exceeds its limit,
it will collapse!
For heaven's sake...
Fatty!
Make another bod... body for Ao Bing now!
Huh?
Making two bodies back-to-back
has completely drained
the Sacred Lotus's energy.
Without a body, won't his soul scatter?
Master, do something!
there's nothing I can do.
It's okay.
I took your place as the Spirit Pearl,
I deserve this.
If my sacrifice
can bring you back to life,
then it's a fair price to pay.
Who asked you to?
I am happy being the Demon Orb.
Don't you dare to die!
Father,
please spare Chentang Pass.
We should stop the mistakes.
This is my final wish.
There has to be other ways.
There has to.
You! Try harder!
Let Ao Bing share your body for now.
Share your body.
Two souls sharing one body,
rejection is inevitable.
The Spirit Pearl and Demon Orb come
from the same source.
Sharing one body
for seven days shouldn't be a problem.
That's it!
Ao Bing, come on up!
Quick!
Okay.
This feels... strange...
Ao Bing, are you here?
Yes, I am.
I can hear your voice in my head!
This is fun!
But this is only a temporary fix.
What happens after seven days?
There's some potion in
the vault of Yu Xu Palace.
Elixir Reparo.
It can restore the divine
power of magical items.
With it,
the Sacred Lotus will bloom again.
But how will you obtain it?
I'll go to the Supreme Lord himself
and beg for it.
Or are you planning to
report on me and the Loongs?
Save a son of the Loongs.
If asking doesn't work,
then we'll just take.
Yu Xu Palace is at the
core of the Chan Sect,
protected by formidable powers.
For my son,
I'll break into the Court
of Heaven if I had to.
Your Majesty, calm down.
I might have a plan.
Chan disciples who excel in their training
can participate in the Ascension Trial.
Passing the trial grants
not only immortality,
but also the right to choose one
ma... magic item from the
Yu Xu Vault as a reward.
Nezha participate in the trial
to obtain the elixir?
No, no, no!
He's beaming with demonic energy!
As soon as he uses his
powers, he'll be exposed!
Isn't Ao Bing sharing Nezha's body?
His divine aura can mask
the demonic energy perfectly.
As long as he passes
the trial within seven days,
not only will we have the el... elixir...
But he can also
achieve immortality!
Then I'm not a demon anymore?
This will save both Ao Bing and Nezha.
Eve... everyone is happy.
This isn't the right thing to do.
Then what do you suggest?
Follow the rules.
Come clean with the Supreme Lord
and trust his judgement.
My wife and I will also plead for mercy,
so the sins of the parents
don't affect the children.
Mere mortals,
you have only decades of life experience,
how dare you lecture me about morality?
Longer than I could remember,
I've lived for thousands of years.
Let me tell you one
truth and one truth only.
If my son die,
I'll have Chentang Pass sink with him.
Stop!
Ao Bing is my friend.
I will save him for sure.
But if you dare to harm Chentang Pass,
I'll smash your Loong Palace
into P-I-E-C-E-S!
Except for Nezha and Taiyi,
no one leaves Chentang Pass from now on.
If in seven days I don't see Elixir Reparo
or the news of my clan gets out,
I'll let Chentang Pass
sink forever.
I don't trust my siblings,
and I can't stay out of my body for long.
The fate of Chentang Pass
is in your hands.
Yes.
Exactly.
There's no message that can't be conveyed
with just a nod.
Lord Li,
we're all here to say goodbye to
Young Master Nezha.
We want to thank him
for saving the entire city.
You're too kind.
My son has caused enough troubles
over the years.
I always knew the Young Master
was destined for greatness.
Look at him,
a wide forehead,
broad face,
prominent nose,
full cheeks and thick lips.
All signs of a true hero!
I've never been wrong in reading faces.
Young Master,
remember to brush your teeth after meals!
Boss,
the Demon Slayers is now re-branded
as the Nezha Gang.
All members will follow your orders.
Young Master, want to practice calligraphy?
I'm here for you!
Young Master, you're three years old now.
It's time to get a girlfriend.
Any interests in instrument?
We're proficient in all of them.
I want to
play shuttlecock.
What?
It's fun.
Anyone?
I'll play with you.
Didn't you always want to
play shuttlecock with me?
Well...
he's a bit hard on the kicks.
Ha ha ha!
I'm a general of war!
Dad.
That's my boy!
How about...
we do it another day?
Nonsense!
Why stop when you're having fun?
It's fine. I'm fine.
I'll join too!
My lady, you don't have to do this.
Are you looking down on me?
I'm also a general of war!
Nezha,
catch this!
how did you miss that?
If only I weren't the Demon Orb...
What was that?
Nothing.
It's time to go.
Before you go,
will you give your mother
a big hug?
Please, people are watching.
Wait.
Here are some snacks I made.
For you and your master on the road.
Okay, okay.
Hey!
I'm not on board yet!
Your body isn't fully fixed.
Don't use too much force.
Alright, alright.
And watch your temper.
Try to stay calm out there.
Without me and your father by your side,
learn to take care of yourself.
You silly child.
What's wrong with just a hug?
That's too much.
It's not a farewell anyway.
Let's move.
Why are you sighing?
Taste bad?
All you know is food.
Look at me.
I'm too worried to even eat!
Have you thought about
how to pass the trial?
What is the trial about?
It'll test the progress
of your cultivation.
In front of the judges,
you must defeat, barehanded,
three demon kings of earth-monster level.
Fighting...
That's my specialty!
But as soon as you give off demonic energy,
your identity will be exposed.
Just let Ao Bing control my body.
His divine energy
will be just as powerful.
Sounds easy.
Let's try.
Nezha,
fully relax your body.
Let Ao Bing take control and fight me.
Ao Bing, what are you doing?
Keep steady!
When a soul inhabits another body,
unless your willpower is much stronger
than the host's,
you won't be able to fully control it.
Nezha, step back.
The harder you push,
the less Ao Bing can control.
Use your leg!
Sweep him, sweep him!
I'm coming...
for you.
Having fun, huh?
We're almost at Yu Xu Palace,
and you're still messing around.
Look at yourself,
what kind of mentor are you?
Stand here and reflect on your mistakes.
No meals until you figure it out!
You're a grown man.
Stop acting like a reckless teenager.
I got it!
The Sleepy-Slumber Pill.
What's that?
Take this, and you'll
fall asleep immediately.
Once you're asleep,
Ao Bing can fully control your body.
Brilliant!
One is enough.
Should've told me...
earlier.
Perfect.
Master Taiyi?
Now this feels like the real deal.
What's wrong?
Don't worry.
I see you've completely
taken over Nezha's body.
Let's go again.
This time, I won't hold back.
You'd better give it your all, too.
I humbly seek your guidance.
Not bad.
Barely able to match my skills.
Master Taiyi,
your nose is bleeding.
Too heaty recently.
Need more water.
No big deal.
Kunlun Mountain! We're here.
I heard a day here
equals a year in the mortal world.
Don't worry.
We're not in the celestial realm yet.
But this many people?
They've all come to seek immortality.
Chan Sect is famous across the world,
and everyone wants to join.
Look at this.
The jasper.
It's the credential of
a Chan Sect immortal.
With it,
you'll receive respect everywhere you go.
I'm telling ya.
Being an immortal is amazing.
Both of your brothers have ascended.
You'll have no problem either.
I mean Nezha's brothers.
His two brothers
are among the best of
the third-generation disciples.
You know
how Nezha always misbehaves, right?
So, I often tell stories about his brothers
to set a good example for him.
Let me tell you something,
Nezha idolizes his brothers.
Oh wow, you're lucky...
to meet the well-known Demon Hunters.
Demon Hunters?
They roam the land, hunting down
demons that wreak havoc on humanity,
keeping the world at peace.
The current leader of the Demon Hunters
is the top disciple of Immortal Wuliang.
Isn't his predecessor Shen Gongbao?
Master Taiyi,
what's that smoke over there?
Oh.
That's the most precious
treasure of Yu Xu Palace,
The Tianyuan Cauldron.
Brother Taiyi,
it's been forever.
Brother Wuliang!
I heard that during Master's seclusion,
you've been in charge of Yu Xu Palace.
I've brought my disciple to participate
in the Ascension Trial.
come at Master Wuliang.
Master Wuliang.
So, you're Nezha?
The reincarnation of the Spirit Pearl?
Oh my!
How remarkable!
The Supreme Lord holds
great expectations for you.
And you sure don't disappoint.
Look at him,
so full of robust vitality.
Giving off a righteous vibe.
The boy's been over training lately.
His state is a bit unstable.
What do you think you're doing?
This is Yu Xu Palace!
I need to pee.
Crana!
Here!
Take the child to the restroom.
I didn't say anything about resting.
Idiot!
Restroom
is where you pee.
The boy's a bit rough.
Please forgive him.
Wow!
So white!
Is the entire palace made of jade?
Where did they get so
much money to buy jade?
The "Yu" in Yu Xu Palace means jade, right?
Then what does the "Xu" mean?
Humble?
Guilty?
Or emptiness?
Is the restroom also made of jade?
Even immortals need to pee?
Does Master Wuliang also... poop?
This is a place of seclusion.
Lower your voice.
How much further is the restroom?
I can't hold it anymore!
Hey, sister, wait for me!
You...
I didn't mean it.
I need to change my skirt.
Go by yourself.
But I don't know where the restroom is.
Go through the corridor,
turn right, then left.
Oh.
Wow.
How fancy it is!
Radical!
Emm...
Am I lost?
Where are you going?
Oh.
I got lost.
Follow me.
Brother, good job raising the Spirit Pearl.
Another great achievement for the Sect.
Not at all.
It's all thanks to Master's guidance.
This Kunlun Dew is a rare elixir.
Normally, it takes six
months to fill a basin.
But today, when I sent someone to check,
it's already full!
Your timing couldn't be better.
Brother,
luck sure favors you, doesn't it?
What's wrong with you?
Can't even drink water properly.
My disciple is a bit crude.
Please forgive him.
My pee is in the water.
My master is a bit crude, too.
Please forgive him.
time is of the essence.
I think Nezha should go through
the trial immediately.
Why the rush?
Let's have a few more drinks first.
No more, please.
Alright then.
My disciple Deero will be the judge.
The next target of Demon Hunters
could go to Nezha.
Brother, excuse us.
Taiyi, my brother,
always so impatient.
The taste of the Dew this year
is especially rich.
Keep using this method in the future.
Yes, master.
Why stop?
It's been six hours,
Master Shen.
Too tired to continue.
Rubbish!
Cultivation allows no laziness.
Without my permission
you'll never stop.
General Li Jing of Chentang Pass
is here to see you.
Master Shen,
yesterday's battle
left many soldiers and civilians
of Chentang Pass injured.
We've run out of medicine.
I humbly ask you to open a path
so that a few doctors can leave
the city to buy supplies.
How bold!
No wonder you're...
Who did that?
You son of a...
I...
St... stop, stop, stop!
Bring me the one
you caught earlier.
He escaped the city during the battle.
General Li, please,
take him ba... back with you.
This is a misunderstanding, Master Shen!
I'm a demon too!
I captured this Yaksha
to clear my son's name.
Now that it's settled,
and since he hasn't done anything worse,
just let him go.
Yes, exactly.
I'm just a small role.
Insignificant.
I don't think you understood me.
No one leaves here, not even a demon.
Let alone humans.
Master Shen, please have mercy.
I'm a demon, too.
We are both villains!
I'm n... not a villain.
Everyone who knows the
secret of the Spirit Pearl
must stay here.
Without medicine,
the injured won't survive.
Master Shen, please,
I'm only asking to save lives.
Sir!
We caught a spy.
This man came from outside the city,
and he injured some of our soldiers.
Lock... lock him up too.
Brother.
Brother, is that you?
You...
Brother, it's me!
Xiaobao?
You haven't been home for centuries.
I miss you so much.
What are you doing here?
Father sent me to find you.
Look,
the compass you gave me.
It tells me where you are.
Father...
how is he doing?
He's great.
Ever since you entered Yu Xu Palace,
father's been full of energy,
like he took some miracle tonic.
You are the only one from our village ever
made it as a Chan Sect immortal.
Now, fellow demons from miles around
are pouring in to train with father.
By the way,
why are you here?
Didn't you promise me before,
once I've achieved human form,
you'd get me into Yu Xu Palace?
Look! I can turn into a human now!
All these years, I've trained so hard,
never rested a day.
You're my role model, big brother.
Glory to Yu Xu, answering heaven's call.
Travel the world, bringing justice to all.
Say, brother,
what are you doing here?
I... I...
Are these sea monsters your subordinates?
Why are you surrounding Chentang Pass?
Well, about that...
Th... this is...
Master Shen is defending Chentang Pass.
Huh?
Evil forces invaded the city.
Master Shen and the
sea clan came to our aid.
On behalf of my people,
I thank you for this noble act.
Don't mention it.
Wow!
Brother, you're incredible!
Is this the demon attacking Chentang Pass?
Ah!
You are a disgrace to all demons!
Shame on you!
Hey,
Xiaobao,
can you
wait a few more years
before going to Yu Xu Palace?
Why?
I can transform into a human now!
It's just that...
I'm preparing for my promotion
to the Twelve Golden Immortals,
so I can't be distracted.
Twelve Golden Immortals?
Once it's done,
I'll take you there,
okay?
No problem, brother!
Your promotion is more important.
I can go to Yu Xu Palace anytime.
Besides,
I haven't quite mastered
the shape-shifting.
I'll go back and practice more.
More.
Xiaobao,
this is what I've saved up since
I entered the palace.
What is it?
Yu Xu Palace gives all disciples
these immortality pills.
Take one
and you ga... gain ten years' worth
of cultivation.
But...
this is too precious.
Brother, you're training for a promotion.
You should keep them.
I don't like how it tastes.
I prefer cultivating on my own.
You... you should bring them back.
Share them with the family.
Father will blame me.
are you not obeying your big brother?
Take the pills and leave now.
This is the front line.
If... if you stay,
I'll be distracted.
Then...
I...
I'll leave.
Brother.
You must make it into the
Twelve Golden Immortals.
I'll keep training myself.
I appreciate your help,
but the stake is too high
for me to let anyone through.
This Yaksha...
you... you bring him back, too.
I wasn't helping you.
I was helping the young one.
A good role model
can change his life.
Wait.
Le... leave me a list
of medicines you need.
I am Nezha, the Third Prince bold.
I slay the demons, I write in rhyme untold.
Today I come to rid the evil's breath.
You wicked fiends, prepare for death!
Still eating?
You are doomed.
Ahhh!
Who do you think you are?
Barging into our Bandits Hill?
So, you're in charge?
and have a taste of my power.
You arrogant spoilt brat.
teach him a lesson.
Show me what you got.
You go.
No, but, boss...
how dare I steal your thunder?
Fighting a child is just embarrassing.
When I say go, you go.
Hey, kid.
Too young,
too naive.
So, I'm willing to let this slide.
You, you...
It's still not too late to
run home to mommy.
What's wrong?
Why are you awake again?
I don't know.
I'm a light sleeper.
All that shaking has jolted me awake.
Damn it.
He took too much of that pills
and now he's immune.
Increase the dose then.
If you insist to stay you might get hurt.
I was going to dodge to the right.
Sorry, I thought it was left.
So weak.
Maybe I should cut in.
He could use a few more years' training.
Not so fast.
He was just teasing the demon.
The boy likes to...
play dumb.
Pills.
I gave you a warning.
Now you know who you're messing with.
Oh no.
The pills have dissolved in the soup!
Then I'll drink the soup.
And you're trying to steal our soup?
This calls for a beating.
Let me.
So gross.
Super Mighty Club Strike!
I told you he was pretending.
I wasn't paying attention.
That didn't count.
Not possible!
You suck!
Step aside!
Watch me kick his butt.
Why did you spit it all out?
The taste is too strong.
I couldn't help it.
Check this out!
Funny!
This isn't working.
We can't win without the pill.
Deero is watching.
I can't give you the pill.
What do we do now?
I got it.
There is another way.
You're not suggesting...
We can eat the puke.
But,
it's disgusting.
What's the big deal?
Remember when I drank Yaksha booger?
This explains a lot.
No pains
no gains.
That's how Nezha defeat fate.
Lives of my parents
and friends are at stake,
and the people of Chentang Pass.
E-A-S-Y P-E-A-S-Y!
With ignoring prejudice
and overcoming inner fears
I will change my destiny.
I kept low-key
until today's show.
Master Taiyi.
Save Nezha first.
Then we'll figure out
a way for Elixir Reparo.
No way.
I don't believe this.
let's do another round.
Fake death?
I'll smash you!
Good thing Nezha got knocked out.
You do suck!
Let me avenge you!
Invincible Whirlwind Punch!
Ahhh!
Do we have to catch them all?
Even leaving one behind
could harm the people here.
Take them all back to Yu Xu Palace.
The Sect will guide them to the right path,
turning evil to good.
What's with the face?
No biggy.
His look switches from time to time.
Spirit Pearl, you know,
not like normal people.
Be more careful next time,
you scared my soul out.
Who's this kid?
Nezha, possibly.
Younger brother of Jinzha and Muzha.
He's the Spirit Pearl reincarnation
appointed by the Supreme Lord.
Not likely, huh?
Hunched back.
Wobbly pace.
Sinking brows and drooping eyes.
Disgusting face.
Not to mention the dark eye circles.
More like a ghost.
Not now.
Brother,
what's the star sign tonight?
Six stars in alignment,
once in a decade.
Whenever six stars align,
this Jade Podium can transmit sound
and images across thousands of miles.
Our brothers scatter all over the world
and finally get together.
Tonight is the night,
the Golden Immortals shall meet.
I haven't ascended to the Twelve yet.
Maybe I shouldn't be included.
It's only a matter of time.
No la, no la.
It's not appropriate at all.
I can't do it, really.
Then why are you sitting up there?
Shut up!
Would it kill you to
see your master thrive?
A Sauna!
Shh!
Brothers and sisters,
I humbly welcome you back to your places.
Greetings, Brother Wuliang!
Allow me to introduce a new member.
Brother Taiyi.
He has fulfilled the master's expectations
and successfully nurtured
the Spirit Pearl reincarnation.
Pay your respect.
The Deification War is imminent.
We are here to discuss the preparation.
Chan Sect is the orthodox of Tao,
so we're destined to win.
But as Jie Sect has
risen rapidly these years,
we must remain vigilant.
Jie Sect,
is where furry and horny beasts gather
and creatures born of mucus and eggs.
This war concerns the survival of our sect.
We must be careful.
Strengthening our power
is the key.
Precisely.
That's why I began preparing early.
Immortality pills,
a total of nine thousands.
Could be allocated according to grades.
This will definitely boost our strength.
How could be so many?
For a hundred years,
our master has tirelessly refined pills
with the Tianyuan Cauldron,
working day and night,
at the cost of his own cultivating.
Brother Wuliang has dedicated himself
to building our sect,
his contributions are to be praised.
Aye, aye.
Besides the Jie Sect,
are there other evil
forces plotting against us?
Master Cihang,
as soon as menacing demons are discovered,
the Demon Hunters will
immediately be sent out.
So, most stray demons pose no threat.
But,
there is one exception.
Who is that?
The Eastern Sea Loongs.
Loongs?
Didn't they surrender to the Court
of Heaven long ago?
No kind could be trusted
except for our own.
To me,
their surrender is merely a facade,
hibernating for a moment.
The Loongs have helped subdue the
abyss monsters for thousands of years.
What's their crime?
But they own great strength.
If they betray us in the war,
the whole situation could be overturned.
But we still can't do that.
Our reputation of righteous
and just is known to all.
If we gratuitously
attack the surrendered,
how will anyone ever trust us?
Aye.
We must not act rashly.
Further deliberation is necessary.
Enough.
They made their points.
And you don't have to be bigoted.
OK.
The time of the six-star
alignment is almost over.
Since there are no other topics,
let's adjourn the meeting.
Brother,
Jinzha and Muzha
are disciples of myself and Brother Puxian.
They have been cultivating here
for many years away from home,
never even met Nezha,
their younger brother.
Since there's still time left
in the six-star alignment,
why not let them
meet for a while?
Great idea.
OMG!
What should I do?
What?
Speaking of my look...
Will my first impression...
Be bad?
Of course not!
Really?
Though slovenly,
you've got strong will.
Though short,
you've got a big heart.
Though ugly,
you're kind inside.
Though you have black eye circles,
piggy nose
I still think
you're truly incredibly great.
And I'm sure your brothers would agree.
Thanks for the compliment.
What are you doing?
You go meet my brothers for me.
Seriously?
How can I do this for you?
No, Nezha.
Nezha!
The boy is a bit shy.
Brother!
Ao Bing,
you cried?
This reminded me of my two brothers.
You have brothers too?
Mm.
I used to.
Having two such wonderful brothers.
You're so lucky.
What were you talking about just now?
They said
they're sorry for not checking
on you all these years.
They asked
how things have been at home,
if your parents are well,
what hobbies you have,
and who your friends are.
They also said
that whatever problems
you may have in the future,
go to them.
And remember, you have two brothers
who will always help and protect you.
Why are you...
Nothing.
It's just sand in my eyes.
You sure it's not the other way around?
Shut up!
I said nothing.
OK. You are the boss here.
I'm not talking to you.
Fine,
I'll stop.
Are you still mad?
Nezha?
Nezha!
Ao Bing,
I've been violent and
unruly since I was young,
making my parents worry all day.
Your father,
though he attacked Chentang Pass,
I know he only risk everything
for your sake.
And today,
my brothers were so kind to me.
Our families have
sacrificed so much for us.
You're a monster,
and I'm a demon.
We're both burdens for our families.
So what if we were born as demons?
Immortal or demon, I make the choice.
Once you are saved,
we must win ourselves a
place among the immortals
so our families won't
have to worry anymore.
Yes!
Only by becoming immortals
can we have everyone's respect.
Deal!
I'm going to become an immortal!
Only with courage and diligence
can great progress be made.
At this speed,
hundred years would still be in vain.
About cultivating,
the priorities are
vitality, energy, and spirit.
If feeling hard,
or exhausted,
it's because you were born demons.
Only by giving it your all
you will have a chance
to change your destiny
and achieve immortality.
Life or death, of none I'm scared,
defying authority is what I've revered.
My fate is mine, not heaven's plan.
This bad boy will become a godly man!
Bravo!
Just a few lines, yet so powerful,
truly inspiring.
A great poem, indeed.
This is something all
of you should learn from.
Really?
Is it that good?
I just made it up.
It is good.
Every word counts,
and encouraging.
A poem like this
shows the ambition of you, young man.
A true young hero
with a bright future ahead!
Oh, come on. It's just fine.
Actually, it still has some tiny flaws.
More like plenty of flaws.
Let me ask you,
what's with those dark eye circles?
It's obvious you stay up late all the time.
Your life is undisciplined,
your diet unhealthy,
and you can't even
manage basic self-control.
How dare you dream of becoming an immortal?
I was born with dark eye circles.
Appearance reflects the
heart, don't you know?
Take a look at yourself in the mirror.
reckless and sloppy.
If you were my disciple,
I'd make you rebuild your human form.
Can be rebuilt?
Then there's hope for my looks, right?
Teach me, please.
I knew you came to find yourself a master.
Listen, kid,
I see you have great ambition,
so I'll take you as my disciple.
Master!
Come,
train with your brothers.
Train for what?
Immortality, of course.
I don't need you to teach me that.
Show me how to be prettier.
You're putting looks before cultivation?
Get your priorities straight.
Are you teaching me or not?
We're no longer master and disciple.
You deserve to have panda eyes for life.
That's too much.
I was going to go easy on you!
Are you challenging me?
Three pills should be enough.
Kid,
go back where you came from.
If you keep disrupting our class,
this could end badly for you.
Apologies.
You're no match for me.
Impressive, kid.
I underestimated you.
Try this!
Yeah, teach this ignorant brat a lesson.
Master will surely win!
So fast!
You saw it?
We have no grudges between us.
You'd better go.
I cannot lose.
You can't even touch me.
Let alone fight.
Hold him tight.
Speedy is junky.
Surrender?
Wait, you are...
You've figured it out finally.
I'm not fast.
I just transform into electric currents,
traveling instantly to any location.
In water,
I am invincible!
Impressive cryo power.
Stay calm.
Try too hard and your body will collapse!
Ice doesn't conduct electricity.
Let's see what else you've got.
Lakes and seas...
By this divine talisman in my hand.
Wind is to rise and rain is to fall.
Swift and Uplift!
Father!
Damn it.
The Rain Summoning Spell.
End this now!
Too late.
You're doomed.
Master!
Master, are you all right?
I wasn't going to take your life.
You didn't have to sacrifice an arm.
All disciples, listen,
take the demons back to the palace.
Yes!
Stop!
Put them down.
All of you, put them down!
May I ask if you are a
member of the Chan Sect?
That's correct.
Ah.
These are all immortals from Yu Xu Palace.
You must not be disrespectful.
Entering Yu Xu Palace
and receiving the teachings
of the righteous path
may not be a bad thing.
All of you, drop your weapons!
Father!
Xiaobao?
How come you're back?
Xiaobao,
stand down!
Xiaobao!
Demon!
How dare you!
No!
Father!
freeze the river now!
You can't escape!
Father!
Go!
Go now!
Run!
Father...
There's no escape.
Step aside.
He's just trying to save his father.
You didn't have to be so brutal.
Hmph.
Panax notoginseng,
cattail pollen,
munjeet,
borneol,
Loong's blood.
One more basket.
Safflower,
angelica,
pseudo-ginseng powder,
sappanwood,
poison nut.
My lord,
we now have everything on the list,
along with a hundred
baskets of sea products.
We happen to be short on food supplies.
Master Shen, a moment, please.
We've prepared a meal.
Would you honor us with your presence?
You...
Thanks to Lord Li's kindness,
I've been taken in as a servant.
He may be a demon,
but he has a good heart.
As long as he behaves,
there's no reason he can't have a future.
I wonder if the dishes suit your taste.
Not...
Not bad.
Then have some more.
Try this liquor as well.
I quit long ago.
Cultivators must sup... suppress desires.
As the saying goes,
one must cut off urges
to perfect the spirit.
Another saying goes,
one must practice
kindness to polish virtue.
Talking won't help.
I've already re... reached
the point of no return.
You can't hide forever.
The truth will come out one day.
If you continue to harm lives
making more mistakes,
even if you can deceive everyone,
you won't be able to fool yourself.
And you will not improve further
on your cultivation,
the essence of which
is doing good deeds
and walking the righteous path.
What nonsense!
You know nothing
about cultivation.
Sir!
Someone is here to see Master Shen.
Brother.
Who did this to you?
Some Taoists.
They attacked.
Father...
had one of his arms
cut off.
Who did it?
His name is...
Ne...
Zha.
Congratulations on passing Level 2.
Please inform Brother Wuliang.
Master is in seclusion refining pills
and has not emerged yet.
Before Level 3,
why don't you rest for a few days?
We only have two days left.
No need.
I'm so fine.
Let's continue the test.
as you wish.
The final test
is the demon Queen of Skull Mountain,
Shi Ji.
Someone is requesting an urgent meeting
with Master Taiyi.
Huh?
Please help us!
It's Chentang Pass.
Something happened!
Dad.
Mom.
Dad?
Mom?
Dad!
Mom!
Calm down.
Let's keep looking.
Keep looking.
I received an urgent report as soon as
I ended seclusion.
Who could have committed
such a horrendous crime?
Master,
according to Shieldos,
they were struck by a tremendous force
and lost consciousness.
When they woke up,
people of Chentang Pass had
already been slaughtered.
We haven't obtained the elixir yet.
Why would they do that?
Brother,
any clue?
No, no.
where did all this lava come from?
Exactly.
There are no volcanoes
for hundreds of miles around.
This is truly bizarre.
Everyone, come quick!
What demon is this?
This is...
left by a Loong's claw.
Impossible!
The Loongs are all in Eastern Sea,
guarding the Suppression Seal.
Not a single one could have left.
Master,
if I remember correctly,
Queen Ao Run of Western Sea
has a special skill
called the Sky...
Sky-Splitting Claw.
Are you saying she used
the Sky-Splitting Claw
to cross into Chentang Pass?
That explains the lava.
It must have been transported
from the purgatory remotely.
But she's watched by
the Loong King of Eastern Sea.
It's impossible for her to cross over.
Then there's only one possibility left.
The thing I worried the most
happened.
The King of Eastern Sea has betrayed us?
This is too serious an accusation.
Could we be wrong?
No.
It's them!
What are you doing?
Don't be impulsive.
Are you heading to the Loong Palace?
That's the direction of Skull Mountain.
The Loongs slaughtered innocent civilians,
committing this unforgivable atrocity.
No need to consult with
fellow Golden Immortals.
I'll strike first and explain later.
Crana,
back to the palace with me.
Summon all the Demon Hunters.
Brother,
Nezha's parents were killed by demons.
We can't let anything happen to the child.
Go with Deero for him now.
Yes.
I know you're heartbroken right now,
but can you please
calm down for a moment?
Can you
take me to the Loong Palace first?
I'll confront my father and master
to get to the bottom of this.
Will that bring my parents back?
Mirror mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest within
ten miles and more?
It's you,
my lady.
And who is the fairest
within a hundred miles?
It's you, my lady.
What about a thousand miles?
It's you.
And ten thousand miles?
And in the whole world?
Still you.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Lie better, at least.
No, no.
I was just trying not to piss you off.
You know what?
Telling the truth won't make me mad.
Seriously?
I, Lady Shi Ji, am
indeed a stunning beauty,
but I know there's always someone better.
Go on and ask then.
Am I the fairest of them all?
No.
Fair enough.
Am I the fairest within ten thousand miles?
What about a thousand miles?
No.
Ten miles?
Nope.
Am I even the fairest on this mountain?
There isn't any other
female in this mountain.
I'm female, too.
You promised you won't get mad.
You are prettier than me?
Help!
How the hell!
Demon, show yourself!
Who are you calling demon?
It's Lady Shi Ji.
Damn kid.
Have we even met?
What the hell are you up to?
You will be exposed.
Let me.
Stay out of it.
You think you can defeat me?
The entire mountain is my body.
I'll see how you can destroy me.
If you use more force,
your body will collapse!
I said,
stay out of it!
Already started!
Crap!
I'm so screwed.
Luckily there's some left.
I shall live to fight another day.
Damn kid.
Just you wait.
Nine-Loong Fire Trap!
No escape!
Oh my!
Reckless child.
Your body has almost gone.
Are you trying to kill yourself?
What's that fire earlier?
Isn't Nezha
a frost mage?
Who... who said that?
Frost, flame, I taught him everything.
His powers are
a combination of ice and fire.
Is that possible?
The Spirit Pearl is endowed
with unparalleled talents.
Can't judge him by normal standards.
Which one of us is the teacher?
You think you know better than me?
I wouldn't dare.
However,
I did sense a strong presence
of demonic energy earlier
About that...
Shi Ji must have released it.
What are you saying, fatty?
I did not...
Was it you? Just tell me, was it?
Say it!
Yes, it was me.
Stop shaking.
I'm about to throw up!
See? I told you.
Nezha,
you've passed three levels.
Today,
I will personally cast
the Ascension Spell for you.
I've been through all of this back there.
I was probably too nervous.
The Ascension Spell is
longer than I remember.
From now on,
you're an Immortal of the Chan Sect.
This Yu Xu Treasure Vault
houses all sorts of rare magic items.
Elixir Reparo.
You can only pick one.
Don't you need more time?
Elixir Reparo.
Yu Xu Palace has sent messengers
to inform the Twelve
about what the Loongs did.
However, due to the great distance,
my brothers and sisters
can't make it here sooner.
This time,
I myself will lead the hunt
on the Loongs.
Nezha,
will you fight alongside me?
Let me go back to Chentang Pass first.
Then we'll seek revenge on the Loong King.
OK.
With your extraordinary combat skills,
you'd be a great help
in destroying the Loong Palace.
I've paid back
everything I owed you.
Wait.
When I get my body back,
I will go with you to
the Loong Palace, okay?
You know well what I'm going to do.
You being there will only make it harder.
Next time we meet,
we're foes instead of friends.
Ugh...
Karma it is.
No, you can't leave!
Your soul will scatter before
you get to the Loong Palace.
Nine-Loong Fire Trap!
Calm down, will you?
won't change anything.
Leave me alone.
Let me out!
No!
I promised Nezha
I'd save you no matter what.
Pah! Pah!
Suffocating!
Who's there?
I'm Immortal Wuliang of the Chan Sect.
Ao Guang,
do you admit your guilt?
So,
you've found out?
Is
Ao Bing still alive?
I'll accept whatever
punishment you give me,
but please spare my son.
Nonsense!
The Court of Heaven ordered your clan
to suppress the sea monsters.
Instead, you colluded with them
and slaughtered Chentang Pass.
What?
The Loongs have committed
an unforgivable crime.
justice shall be done.
Encompassed are the earth and the skies.
Unleash the power with boundless might.
Let the Tianyuan rise and stand tall.
Reign supreme above them all.
Open Cauldron!
Show yourselves!
What have you done to Chentang Pass?
Didn't big brother tell us
to follow Master Shen's orders?
Shen Gongbao?!
Speaking of the emergency,
you should focus on present.
My King,
we can't sit here and wait to die!
If I go into battle,
the Suppression Seal will...
Leave that to us.
Joining all our powers,
we can hold it for long enough.
Fine.
I've had enough!
You wretched demon!
This is an once-in-a-millennium chance
for revenge.
Break out of the purgatory!
Destroy the Loong Palace!
Soul Blade!
Old fool!
Taste my sword!
Releasing demonic energy like this...
aren't you afraid of
exposing your identity?
I told you,
if you dared to harm Chentang Pass,
I would smash your palace into PIECES!
Is Ao Bing dead?
Move! Out of my way!
Rise!
Do you have a death wish?
Let's see how long your body can take it.
I don't care if I live or die.
As long as you're dead!
Now is the time!
Look what you've done!
Is annihilation for all
really what you want?
The chains.
Even the Eastern Sea Loong King
can't match your power.
I was right after all.
You're exactly what the Chan Sect needs.
Your parents spent
their lives fighting evil.
From now on,
you must carry on their legacy
and eliminate all the demons.
Let me avenge your loss
by turning these bastards into pills.
Escort me!
Yes, master!
Nezha!
Dad!
Mom!
Nezha!
Son, are you alright?
Your body...
I... I...
They already know
about you and Ao Bing.
I... I...
I thought...
I'd never see you again.
Master is still casting the spell.
We need to buy as much time as we can.
Nezha,
it wasn't my father who
slaughtered Chentang Pass.
The real culprit
is him, the Immortal Wuliang!
Shieldos!
Loongs.
Brother,
it's been a while.
Why are you here?
Shen Gongbao,
you collude with the Loongs.
What are you up to?
I should be ask... asking you.
You captured my father.
What are you up to?
Who said I captured your father?
Only you know my family's situation.
If you didn't give the order,
why would Nezha and the Demon Hunters
hunt my father down?
And my little brother's arrow wound...
It's obviously
caused by your disciple, Deero!
There's the talent I recruited myself.
Nothing slips past you.
After all, I've done your dirty work
for so many years.
I can also guess your purpose here
putting up a show in Chentang Pass.
You are trying to fram... frame the Loongs,
aren't you?
Is this how you repay me,
your brother and mentor?
You've always use...
used me for your benefit.
Between you and me,
there's only grudge, not gratitude.
May I interest you in a deal?
Master Immortal.
As the overseer of Yu Xu Palace,
you must know the spell to
unhinge the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
I do.
So what?
You... you are going to rebel?
A thousand years ago, the four of us
fought the celestial realm together.
Who's then betrayed us and
cast us into the purgatory?
Now Wuliang is targeting Ao Guang,
that's exactly what we want.
I've long heard that Immortal Wuliang
recruit talents without bias.
I trust it you know well what we can do.
If you can free us from the purgatory
and help us achieve immortality,
we are willing to offer our humble service.
Plus the secret of the Spirit Pearl
and the Demon Orb.
The Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb?
Whe... where's your
spirit of fighting back?
We were young and ignorant!
A thousand years of imprisonment
has taught us about the rules
and the rulers.
Smart.
But you're so unpredictable.
How can I trust you?
Unless you let me place on you...
We are willing.
The three Loongs willingly agreed
to let Wuliang place a curse on them.
If they dare to disobey in the future,
Wuliang can take their lives at any time.
Wuliang then fulfilled his promise,
freeing them from the
Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
Whenever a powerful force is discovered,
he orchestrates massacres,
frames others,
and sends troops to capture them.
According to Shen Gongbao,
he had carried out many
such tasks for Wuliang
in exchange for a chance
to join the Chan Sect.
This time, Wuliang came
to destroy Chentang Pass
and frame the Loongs of Eastern Sea.
One thing led to another,
he ended up recruiting
the three Loong kings.
And from them,
he learned the secret of the Demon Orb
and the Spirit Pearl.
they deliberately left
two clueless survivors
to tell Yu Xu Palace what happened.
Seeing no hope of breaking through,
Shen Gongbao came up with a plan.
He had the Yaksha petrify us,
then hide us in the sewers.
Later, he waited for the
right time to revive us.
And you?
My families are gone.
I have nothing left to hold onto.
Over there!
The demons captured by the Demon Hunters
are not, as outsiders think,
being reformed in Yu Xu Palace.
Instead, they are thrown into the
Tianyuan Cauldron by Wuliang,
refined into pills of immortality
to strengthen the Chan Sect's power.
Brother,
how could you commit such atrocities?
How...
How are you going to face our master
and the teachings we received?
Now that you know what Wuliang did,
you should stop before it's too late.
Take him back to the palace
to face punishment from the Supreme Lord.
The Demon Hunters were personally trained
by Master Wuliang.
Do you think a few words would turn us
against him?
So,
I was wrong about the Loongs.
Let them go!
Let me help.
You betrayed us?
We learned that from you, Big Brother.
Back then, in order to protect our kind,
I had no choice!
Well, in order to protect myself now,
Neither do I.
My King, wait for us!
Don't leave us behind!
My King, take us with you!
My King! My King!
You've all been sold out!
Loong King of Southern Sea.
Loong King of Northern Sea.
Loong Queen of Western Sea.
Nephew,
it's playtime with your uncle.
Take my spear!
Take my axe!
Take my wheel!
Take my wheel times a hundred!
Two hundreds!
Three hundreds!
Enough, huh?
Bullshit!
There weren't that many.
Your body is still unstable.
Don't exhaust yourself.
For my mistakes,
I would give my life
for freeing the Loongs.
Young and vicious.
Let me have some fun with you, little one.
Bullying a child,
shameless and vile!
Hey!
How dare you hit your master's brother!
Bullying an uncle,
eat a knuckle!
This won't do.
This is a mess.
Then let's make it an even bigger one.
How about some vapor?
Sure.
Take them down!
Watch out for sneaking!
There you are.
Careful, it's me!
My apology.
Nezha!
Ah!
Surprise!
LOL!
Transformation Spell?
Are you insane?
You can't fool me.
Hmm.
What are you...
She sells seashells by the seashore.
What?
You don't know the code.
Imposter!
So you really are an imposter!
Unbelievable!
Serves you right.
Code.
Eh... he sells bells in the big well?
Wrong!
It's "she sells seashells by the seashore
and the shells she
sells all smell for sure".
I'm the real one!
How come I don't know this code?
We just made it up!
Can you make it easier?
Too hard!
You idiot!
Don't come near me!
Imposter!
I'm the real Ao Shun!
Crap! You don't know the code!
Neither do you!
That's true.
Does it mean I'm an imposter, too?
My goodness.
Tai Chi flows in harmony divine,
Five elements perfectly align.
True fire of Samadhi ignites the gold.
A perfect pill, its power unfolds.
Swift and Uplift!
Why are you so scared?
We used to bathe in lava like it's nothing.
Hot! Hot!
Oh no!
It's the true fire of Samadhi.
What are you looking at?
If anyone should eat this, it's me!
Yum.
Let go of my father!
Freeze!
What a Spirit Pearl!
Perfect match with the Demon Orb.
Ao Bing!
Hyah!
Freeze!
The Heart-Piercing Curse.
Since I already knew your true identities,
how could I not have a backup plan?
This is impossible!
That curse is quite complex.
When did you cast it?
Oh...
That's why the Ascension
Spell took so long.
You slipped in something.
You old fart!
Even the Demon Orb
won't be able to break the
Heart-Piercing Curse so quick.
A thousand spikes have pierced
through your nerves and veins.
Forcing any movement
will only result in your body
being torn apart.
No wonder I couldn't sense any living aura.
You were petrified.
But alive.
Only hurt Nezha.
The Spirit Pearl
and the Demon Orb
are precious treasures.
I could treat you well
but now only for pill.
Ao Bing!
You...
you're still alive!
Ungh!
It's the Heart-Piercing
Curse casted by Wuliang.
And he was the one that slaughtered
Chentang Pass framing it on the Loongs.
Father,
Nezha was deceived.
Don't blame him.
Whatever you want to do, do it to me.
Leave my parents out of this.
Killing you won't change anything.
We're all doomed to die here.
If anyone still holds grudges,
be my guest.
Brother,
the Chan Sect has a noble reputation,
how could you commit
such a horrible clanger?
Don't make more mistakes!
Why don't you go back
and confess to Master?
I'll plead for mercy on your behalf.
You...
indiscriminate fool!
Should the immortals'
place in the world is secured
or you ungrateful slackers are half as
diligent as the demons,
I wouldn't have wasted
this much time and efforts!
Even if it leads to my own doom
and infamy,
I did it for the eternal
dominance of Chan Sect.
Conscience...
conscience...
My conscience is clear.
Another one is done.
I can't possibly eat any more.
You should try some.
Thanks.
When my fins are done,
you should try some too.
The claws are ready as well.
We should swop and share.
What's going on?
My body...
He's become a pill!
I'm still so young.
I don't want to die.
No, let me out.
Help!
Stay calm!
Focus all your energy!
Hold on for as long as you can.
Son!
Your power is greater than mine.
You can get through.
If you can hold out
until the heart-piercing curse fades,
you'll have a chance to escape.
The heart-piercing curse
takes at least six hours.
I'm afraid...
I won't be able to last that long.
My lady.
Wake up, mom.
Nezha, Nezha?
Nezha.
I'm here, Mom.
You guys must not give up.
Don't worry about us.
Try to
stay focus.
I'm fine, Mom.
I don't feel the fire.
Nothing kills you, kiddo.
If I am correct,
flames of the Demon Orb
and the true fire of Samadhi
share the same origin.
Then the Tianyuan Cauldron can't harm you.
That's right.
My mistake.
Don't bother.
This is just my avatar.
As I suspected, the Demon Orb
is indestructible.
No wonder the Supreme Lord had
to destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven.
Nezha,
I see you're a good son.
How about I give you
a chance to prove that?
The Oblivion Pill.
Swallow it
and I'll release your parents.
What do you say?
I may be ruthless,
but I always keep my promises.
Otherwise, all those elites of the demons
wouldn't swear loyalty to me.
As long as you swallow it,
I swear to Heaven,
I won't harm your parents.
What are you doing?
Using his parents' lives to threaten a kid?
And you call yourself a god?
You aren't even worthy to be a human.
Nezha,
leave us be.
You must live.
Hold on until the
heart-piercing curse is broken
or your two brothers find you.
You really think I can't
kill the Demon Orb?
It's just a matter of time.
Once you're dead,
I have a hundred ways to destroy him.
I just don't want to die for nothing.
Why won't you let me?
Why won't you?
If your trade your life for ours,
do you think we could live in peace?
Nezha.
No, mom.
It'll hurt you.
It's okay.
This is the end.
I just want to hug you one last time.
Mom.
I guess I won't get to see you grow up.
From now on,
you'll have to walk your own path.
I... I'm useless.
Useless.
I was born a demon,
and have always caused you pain.
I wanted so badly,
to make you proud.
This is all my fault.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Every day I spent with you,
I was so happy.
I never cared
whether you were an immortal
or a demon.
All I know is
you are my son.
Mommy
will always
love...
Nezha, stay calm!
Stop!
Your body will be torn apart!
The True Fire of Samadhi
has compensated for
the fire need for body rebuilding.
Nezha's physical form
is complete now!
Dad,
take care of Mom.
Help me break the cauldron!
They are absorbing the energy
of the Tianyuan Cauldron!
Roota Maxima!
Demon Hunters, by my command,
march!
Father,
you need to save your
energy for self-protection.
We've been backing down
for far too long.
We thought if we gave everything,
then Wuliang would let us live.
But in the end, they still want us dead.
If that's what they want,
then we'll fight them to death!
Yes, let's fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
We can't let them out!
Do not give up!
Hang in there!
Make it...
break!
The cauldron!
My cauldron!
There goes the foundation of Chan Sect!
Kill all these bastards!
Attack!
You ungrateful traitors.
Can't tell right from wrong!
Roaring Loong Waves!
So those two minions
of his are monsters too.
Demons, immortals...
it's all part of your trickery!
You despicable lowlife.
How dare you oppose me!
Witness my true powers!
I'll give you two
one last chance because I value talents.
Surrender now
and I'll grant you immortality.
Hell with immortality!
I'm all demon.
So what?
You claim to be a guiding light,
but all you do is bully the weak,
and bring chaos to the world.
You are the real evil!
Ignorant fools,
the immortals rule the world.
Siding with the powerful
is the only way out.
Either accept that or
you'll have no place to run to.
If no place to go,
I will open up one myself!
If not accepted,
I will overturn!
Master!
My face...
You fools broke my Ageless Spell!
Old fart.
Ba... back to the palace.
Wait for me!
My father plans to lead the Loongs
deep into the ocean to hide away.
Now that your identity is exposed,
why don't you come with us?
No.
I've been hiding all my life,
concealing myself
until there was nowhere to run.
Now I finally know how to face the world.
Wuliang is one of the
most powerful immortals
and is trusted by the Supreme Lord.
He may not fall so easily.
Plus, immortals and
demons walk different paths,
like water and fire.
Immortals, demons...
Those are just excuses for controlling
those who are different.
So what?
You think you can change that?
I want to try.
Perhaps I'm too old
to fight against the world.
Ao Bing.
I know that
once you've made up your mind,
you'll always follow through.
My son,
in the past,
I put too much a burden on you,
never even
cared what you think.
I apologize.
I only wanted to use my experience
to give you a good life.
But now I see,
the experience of the older generation
is but the past,
and may not be right for you.
You must walk your own path.
From now on,
follow your heart.
I knew you'd come back.
Why?
Because we are both too young.
Too young to fear.
Master,
Your face...
It's fine.
Crana already took care of it.
The cauldron is destroyed
and the Chan Sect is not a sure-win.
And we've committed an unforgivable crime.
We must act before the Master
comes out of seclusion.
Come on,
let's go see him.
Is the holding cell hidden enough?
No one else will come here.
The cell is also shielded from magic.
And gate can only be opened
by you and the only guard.
Hmm.
Slacking.
Dozing off.
What's going on?
This gate
works with face-recognition.
Since your appearance has changed,
you need to re-register.
Go ahead.
Are you mocking me?
I curse you to sleep for ten years.
You've suffered,
my brother.
It is you who have suffered, brother.
Who... who did this to you?
Hmph.
Do you know why I recruited you back then?
I needed a demon.
When the Deification War comes,
I will entrust you with an important task.
Delusional.
Father!
Don't worry.
He's still breathing.
Let me place a curse on you,
and your father will
live a comfortable life
at Yu Xu Palace.
Your two guests have arrived.
Think about it.
Hmm?
The medicine is working.
What should we do now?
Who else can open the gate?
Ten years...
Jinzha of Cloud Cave, Wulong Mountain,
Muzha of White Crane
Cave, Jiugong Mountain,
reporting back to duty.
Master,
bear with me a little longer.
I think it's enough.
It seems
the left eye still isn't swollen enough.
Add some more to the right cheek, too.
Wait.
Were you just laughing at me?
We wouldn't dare.
Master, you're suffering.
It pains our hearts to see you like this.
Really?
We solemnly swear
to heaven and earth.
Alright, alright.
I might have...
beaten too hard.
What?
Don't worry.
Put it on, we'll come back when it heals.
Master, you're meant for greatness.
This is all for the
future of the Chan Sect.
Let's try a few more times,
we'll get it right eventually.
Don't let him go!
Quick!
Do it!
Let go of me!